tarotforum.net 2018-10-06

# Privacy Policy

Aeclectic Tarot is committed to protected your privacy. We don't share your personal information with anyone except to comply with the law, develop our websites, products or services, or protect our rights.

This privacy policy describes how we use personal information collected through visitors, members and subscribers to Aeclectic Tarot ([www.aeclectic.net](http://www.aeclectic.net/)) and the Aeclectic Tarot Forum ([www.tarotforum.net](http://www.tarotforum.net/)).

If you have any questions about our privacy policy, or deleting or correcting your personal information, please contact us.

We collect personal information such as your name and email address when you subscribe to one of the Aeclectic Tarot email newsletters or make a purchase directly from Aeclectic Tarot. Newsletters may be sent up to three times a month; special offers, or information about our new products or services may be sent on an occasional basis. You will be able to unsusbcribe at any time through replying or an unsubscribe link in the email. Email addresses collected will never be sold, traded, given away, shared or otherwise distributed, with the exception of our email delivery provider. 

We collect personal information such as email addresses, locations, IP addresses, and birthdates as part of your separate membership to the Aeclectic Tarot Forum, though you may visit the Forum without registering. This personal information is used for the purpose of running and improving the Aeclectic Tarot Forum, and will not be distributed, sold, traded or otherwise shared outside of Aeclectic Tarot staff, unless prior permission is given. You may receive email notifications and newsletters from the Forum but you can unsubscribe at any time through an unsubscribe link in each email. 

We use a common website feature known as a cookie to track aggregate information about use of our website. We do not store any of your personal information in cookies. You can refuse cookies by turning them off in your browser, however, Aeclectic Tarot's functionality may be affected.

Ads appearing on any of our websites may be delivered to visitors by advertising partners, who may set cookies. These cookies allow the ad server to recognize your computer each time they send you an online advertisement to compile information about you or others who use your computer. This information allows ad networks to, among other things, deliver targeted advertisements that they believe will be of most interest to you. This privacy policy covers the use of cookies by Aeclectic Tarot and does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers. 

Like most websites, we use third-party services to compile non-personal information and statistics on visitor behaviour and browsing habits, such as page views, visits, unique visitors, etc. We may share this non-personally identifiable information where needed to improve the website. 

We do not collect sensitive financial information, and at no time does Aeclectic Tarot have access to your credit card number or financial information. Credit card and customer financial transactions are handled by [PayPal](http://www.paypal.com/). 

We do not knowingly collect information on those under thirteen years of age. Our website, products and services are all directed to people who are at least thirteen years old or older.

We link to other third-party websites from Aeclectic Tarot and the Aeclectic Tarot Forum. We are not responsible for the privacy practices of other websites. 

We may make changes to this privacy policy at any time, at our discretion. By using our website, you consent to our privacy policy.

Some of the links on Aeclectic Tarot and the Aeclectic Tarot Forum are affiliate links, which means that we may earn a commission if you click on the link or make a purchase using the link. When you make a purchase, the price you pay will be the same whether you use the affiliate link or go directly to the vendor's website using a non-affiliate link. 

Amazon affiliate disclosure: Aeclectic Tarot is a participant in the Amazon Services LLC Associates Program, an affiliate advertising program designed to provide a means for sites to earn advertising fees by advertising and linking to Amazon.com.

We may receive free products in return for reviews or inclusion on Aeclectic Tarot. We may accept also payment for deck and book listings in order to speed up their addition to the website. This does not affect the rating, review or treatment of the product or service. 

All material on Aeclectic Tarot Forum and the Aeclectic Tarot Forum is provided for general information purposes only and does not constitute medical, legal, financial, or other professional advice on any subject matter.

Aeclectic Tarot  
PO Box 1532  
Coorparoo DC  
4151 QLD  
Australia
